Guide to the Annina Nosei Gallery Archive 1963-2009 MSS.298
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Artist Files, 1963-2004; 200736
  - Subseries C: Visuals Binders, 205262
    - Sy Ross; Tod Wizon; Ira Richer, undated; 208989 (Album AW)
    - Salomé; Castelli, undated; 208959 (Album AX)
    - Cheri Samba, undated; 208990 (Album AY)
    - Teresa Serrano, undated; 208991 (Album AZ)
    - Marco Tirelli; Flechemuller, undated; 208992 (Album BA)
    - Jenny Watson, undated; 208993 (Album BB)
  - Subseries D: Material Separated from Master Slides Binders, 204163
    Series comprises mostly photographic prints and transparencies, with some slides, polaroids, and paper materials, used to inventory and promote works sold through Annina Nosei Gallery.
    The order of folders in this subseries follows the order of binders in Series III, Subseries B. Artists' names in folder titles below that appear in brackets (e.g., "[From "Jose Bedia"]")were taken from the tabbed dividers that originally organized the material in the binders.
    - Master Slides A-C [From "Jose Bedia"] [1/3], undated; 209305 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Master Slides A-C [From "Jose Bedia"] [2/3], undated; 209306 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Master Slides A-C [From "Jose Bedia"] [3/3], undated; 209307 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Master Slides A-C [From "Mike Bidlo;" Alighiero Boetti"], undated; 209308 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Master Slides C-G ["Abraham David Christian"], undated; 209309 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Master Slides C-G [Back Pocket], undated; 209310 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Master Slides H-M [Front Pocket], undated; 209311 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Master Slides M-O ["Allan McCollum"], undated; 209312 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Master Slides M-O [From "Stephen Mueller"], undated; 209313 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Master Slides M-O [Back Pocket], undated; 209314 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Subseries E: Material Separated from Visuals Binders, 204164
    Subseries comprises material separated from Series III, Subseries C, due to some aspect of the material that made it unsuitable to be placed in a binder.
    The order of folders in this subseries follows the order of binders in Series III, Subseries C. Each folder represents one binder sleeve; for example, when all the material has been removed from the ninth sleeve of the "Pizzi Cannella" binder in Subseries C, it is placed in a folder, which is then labeled "Pizzi Cannella [Binder Sleeve 9/12]." When only some of the material is removed from a sleeve, it is noted in the folder title as "[From Binder Sleeve x]" (e.g., Pizzi Cannella [From Binder Sleeve 4/12]").
    General Note
    The folder labeled "[Izumi Chiaraluce Binder]" contains the entirety of the binder since it is mostly paper material.
    - Ghada Amer [Front Pocket], undated; 209326 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Ghada Amer [Binder Sleeve 1/2], undated; 209327 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Ghada Amer [Back Pocket], undated; 209328 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Karl Appel; Francois Boisrond; Georges Rousse [Front Pocket], undated; 209329 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Karl Appel; Francois Boisrond; Georges Rousse [From Binder Sleeve 1], undated; 209331 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Karl Appel; Francois Boisrond; Georges Rousse [Back Pocket], undated; 209330 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Argentina; Fabian Burgos; Pablo Siquier; Martin Larralde [Front Pocket], undated; 209332 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Argentina; Fabian Burgos; Pablo Siquier; Martin Larralde [Binder Sleeve 7/13], undated; 209333 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Argentina; Fabian Burgos; Pablo Siquier; Martin Larralde [Back Pocket], undated; 209334 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [Front Pocket], undated; 209335 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 11/13], undated; 209336 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 12/13], undated; 209337 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 13/13], undated; 209338 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [Front Pocket], undated; 209339 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [From Binder Sleeve 1/21], undated; 209340 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [From Binder Sleeve 7/21], undated; 209341 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [From Binder Sleeve 13/21], undated; 209342 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [From Binder Sleeve 14/21], undated; 209343 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow [Back Pocket], undated; 209344 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Fabian Burgos [Binder Sleeve 2/12], undated; 209345 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Fabian Burgos [Binder Sleeve 3/12], undated; 209346 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Fabian Burgos [Binder Sleeve 12/12], undated; 209347 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Pizzi Cannella [Front Pocket], undated; 209348 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Pizzi Cannella [From Binder Sleeve 1/12], undated; 209349 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Pizzi Cannella [From Binder Sleeve 4/12], undated; 209350 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Pizzi Cannella [Binder Sleeve 9/12], undated; 209351 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Pizzi Cannella [Back Pocket], undated; 209352 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Fernando Canovas [Front Pocket], undated; 209353 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 2/28], undated; 209354 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Fernando Canovas [Binder Sleeve 3/28], undated; 209355 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Fernando Canovas [Binder Sleeve 4/28], undated; 209356 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Fernando Canovas [Binder Sleeve 5/28], undated; 209357 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 17/28], undated; 209358 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 18/28], undated; 209359 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 19/28], undated; 209360 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 20/28], undated; 209361 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Fernando Canovas [Binder Sleeve 21/28], undated; 209362 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 22/28], undated; 209363 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 23/28], undated; 209364 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Fernando Canovas [Binder Sleeve 24/28], undated; 209365 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 25/28], undated; 209366 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 27/28], undated; 209367 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Fernando Canovas [From Binder Sleeve 28/28], undated; 209368 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Fernando Canovas [Loose Material] [1/5], undated; 209369 (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Fernando Canovas [Loose Material] [2/5], undated; 209370 (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Fernando Canovas [Loose Material] [3/5], undated; 209371 (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Fernando Canovas [Loose Material] [4/5], undated; 209372 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Fernando Canovas [Loose Material] [5/5] [Unlabeled Folder], undated; 209373 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - [Izumi Chiaraluce Binder], undated; 209141 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Entire contents of binder. See General Note, above.
    - Chuck Connelly [Front Pocket], undated; 209142 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Chuck Connelly [From Binder Sleeve 1/23], undated; 209143 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Chuck Connelly [From Binder Sleeve 10/23], undated; 209144 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Chuck Connelly [Back Pocket], undated; 209145 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Ceccobelli; Chia; Commandeur; Colombo [Front Pocket], undated; 209146 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Ceccobelli; Chia; Commandeur; Colombo [Binder Sleeve 1/8], undated; 209147 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - [Arturo Duclos] [Front Pocket 1/2], undated; 209148 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - [Arturo Duclos] [Front Pocket 2/2], undated; 209149 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - [Arturo Duclos] [Binder Sleeve 7/7], undated; 209150 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Arturo Elizondo [Front Pocket], undated; 209154 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Arturo Elizondo [Binder Sleeve 2/7], undated; 209155 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Arturo Elizondo [Binder Sleeve 3/7], undated; 209156 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Arturo Elizondo [Binder Sleeve 4/7], undated; 209157 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Arturo Elizondo [Back Pocket], undated; 209158 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Front Pocket], undated; 209159 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Binder Sleeve 1/14], undated; 209160 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Binder Sleeve 2/14], undated; 209161 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Binder Sleeve 6/14], undated; 209162 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Binder Sleeve 10/14], undated; 209163 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [From Binder Sleeve 11/14], undated; 209164 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Back Pocket], undated; 209165 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Galan [Back Pocket 3/3], undated; 209166 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Julio Galan New [Front Pocket], undated; 209167 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Julio Galan New [Back Pocket] [1/2], undated; 209168 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Julio Galan New [Back Pocket] [2/2], undated; 209169 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Danielle Galliano [Front Pocket], undated; 209170 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Danielle Galliano [Back Pocket], undated; 209171 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Vincent Gallo [Front Pocket], undated; 209172 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Vincent Gallo [Back Pocket], undated; 209173 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Vincent Gallo [Loose Material], undated; 209174 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 4/14], undated; 209175 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 5/14], undated; 209176 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 6/14], undated; 209177 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 7/14], undated; 209178 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2] [Back Pocket], undated; 209179 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Tsibi Geva [2/2] [From Binder Sleeve 1/1], undated; 209180 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Graciela Hasper [Front Pocket], undated; 209181 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Graciela Hasper [Back Pocket], undated; 209182 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - K.H. Hodicke; Koberling [Front Pocket], undated; 209183 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - K.H. Hodicke; Koberling [Binder Sleeve 1/6], undated; 209184 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - K.H. Hodicke; Koberling [Binder Sleeve 2/6], undated; 209185 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - K.H. Hodicke; Koberling [Binder Sleeve 4/6], undated; 209186 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - K.H. Hodicke; Koberling [Back Pocket], undated; 209187 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Kuitca [1] [Front Pocket], undated; 209188 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Kuitca [1] [From Binder Sleeve 5/30], undated; 209189 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Kuitca [1] [Binder Sleeve 26/30], undated; 209190 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Kuitca [1] [Binder Sleeve 27/30], undated; 209191 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Kuitca [1] [Binder Sleeve 28/30], undated; 209192 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Kuitca [1] [Binder Sleeve 29/30], undated; 209193 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Kuitca [1] [Binder Sleeve 30/30], undated; 209194 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Kuitca [1] [Back Pocket], undated; 209195 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Kuitca [2] [Back Pocket], undated; 209196 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - [Helmut] Middendorf [Binder Sleeve 1/12], undated; 209197 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - [Helmut] Middendorf [Binder Sleeve 2/12], undated; 209198 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - [Helmut] Middendorf [Binder Sleeve 8/12], undated; 209199 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - [Helmut] Middendorf [Binder Sleeve 9/12], undated; 209200 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - [Helmut] Middendorf [Back Pocket], undated; 209201 (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - Paul D. Miller/Gianmarco Montesano [Front Pocket], undated; 209202 (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Paul D. Miller/Gianmarco Montesano [Back Pocket], undated; 209203 (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Sabrina Mirri; Schifano [Front Pocket], undated; 209206 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Sabrina Mirri; Schifano [From Binder Sleeve 3/8], undated; 209207 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Sabrina Mirri; Schifano [Binder Sleeve 5/8], undated; 209208 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Sabrina Mirri; Schifano [Binder Sleeve 6/8], undated; 209209 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Sabrina Mirri; Schifano [Back Pocket], undated; 209210 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Stephen Mueller [Front Pocket], undated; 209211 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Stephen Mueller [Binder Sleeves], undated; 209212 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Stephen Mueller [Back Pocket], undated; 209213 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Shirin Neshat Inventory [Loose Material], undated; 209214 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Shirin Neshat Inventory [Binder Sleeve 2/2], undated; 209215 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Shirin Neshat Inventory [Back Pocket], undated; 209216 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Loose Material], undated; 209217 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 2/20], undated; 209218 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 3/20], undated; 209219 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 9/20], undated; 209220 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 10/20], undated; 209221 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 11/20], undated; 209222 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 12/20], undated; 209223 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 13/20], undated; 209224 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 14/20], undated; 209225 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 15/20], undated; 209226 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 16/20], undated; 209227 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 18/20], undated; 209228 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 19/20], undated; 209229 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 20/20], undated; 209299 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Back Pocket], undated; 209230 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Donald Newman [1/2] [Front Pocket], undated; 209231 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Donald Newman [1/2] [From Binder Sleeve 1/13], undated; 209232 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Donald Newman [1/2] [From Binder Sleeve 2/13], undated; 209233 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Donald Newman [2/2] [From Binder Sleeve 4/7], undated; 209234 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Donald Newman [2/2] [From Binder Sleeve 5/7], undated; 209235 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Donald Newman [2/2] [Back Pocket], undated; 209236 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Nunzio [Binder Sleeve 1/6], undated; 209237 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Nunzio [Binder Sleeve 6/6], undated; 209238 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Nunzio [From Back Pocket], undated; 209300 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Front Pocket], undated; 209239 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [From Binder Sleeve 1/13], undated; 209240 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Binder Sleeve 3/13], undated; 209241 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Binder Sleeve 5/13], undated; 209242 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Binder Sleeve 6/13], undated; 209243 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Binder Sleeve 7/13], undated; 209244 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Binder Sleeve 8/13], undated; 209245 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Manuel Ocampo [Back Pocket] [1/2], undated; 209246 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Manuel Ocampo [Back Pocket] [2/2], undated; 209247 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Manuel Ocampo [Loose Folder "Ocampo" in Binder], undated; 209248 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Palmieri Paladino [1/2] [From Binder Sleeve 10/12], undated; 209249 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Palmieri Paladino [1/2] [From Binder Sleeve 11/12], undated; 209255 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Palmieri Paladino [1/2] [From Binder Sleeve 12/12], undated; 209256 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Palmieri Paladino [2/2] [Front Pocket], undated; 209257 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Palmieri Paladino [2/2] [From Binder Sleeve 3/13], undated; 209258 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Palmieri Paladino [2/2] [Binder Sleeve 13/13], undated; 209259 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Palmieri Paladino [2/2] [Back Pocket], undated; 209260 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Liliana Porter [Loose Material], undated; 209261 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Liliana Porter [From Binder Sleeve 1/4], undated; 209262 (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - Liliana Porter [From Binder Sleeve 2/4], undated; 209263 (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - Liliana Porter [From Binder Sleeve 4/4], undated; 209264 (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - Sy Ross, Tod Wizon, Ira Richer [Front Pocket], undated; 209265 (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - Sy Ross, Tod Wizon, Ira Richer [Loose Folder], undated; 209266 (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - Sy Ross, Tod Wizon, Ira Richer [Back Pocket] [Photos from Envelope and Exhibition Cards], undated; 209267 (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - Salomé; Castelli [Front Pocket], undated; 209268 (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - Salomé; Castelli [Binder Sleeve 1/8], undated; 209269 (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - Salomé; Castelli [Back Pocket], undated; 209270 (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - Cheri Samba, undated; 209271 (Box 35, Folder 63)
    - Cheri Samba [Back Pocket], undated; 209272 (Box 35, Folder 64)
    - Teresa Serrano [Front Pocket], undated; 209273 (Box 35, Folder 65)
    - Teresa Serrano [Back Pocket], undated; 209274 (Box 35, Folder 66)
    - Marco Tirelli; Flechemuller [Front Pocket], undated; 209275 (Box 35, Folder 67)
    - Marco Tirelli; Flechemuller [From Binder Sleeve 10/13], undated; 209276 (Box 35, Folder 68)
    - Marco Tirelli; Flechemuller [Back Pocket], undated; 209277 (Box 35, Folder 69)
    - Jenny Watson [From Front Pocket], undated; 209278 (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - Subseries F: Polaroids, 204165
    Series comprises Polaroid instant photographs from a box labeled "Polaroids."
    Polaroid photographs were originally sorted with dividers. The original order has been maintained, including the dividers. The labels of the dividers have been preserved here. Where Polaroids from one artist were found under another artist's label, or when there are no labeled dividers (as in the beginning of Binder BC), the artist's name has been provided in brackets by the archivist to aid the researcher.
    - [Stephen Mueller], undated; 209001 (Album BC)
    - [Emily Cheng], undated; 209507 (Album BC)
    - A, undated; 209002 (Album BC)
    - Appel, undated; 209003 (Album BC)
    - B, undated; 209004 (Album BC)
    - Brauntuch, undated; 209005 (Album BC)
    - Bowen, undated; 209450 (Album BC)
    - Bowes, undated; 209451 (Album BC)
    - Brenner, undated; 209452 (Album BC)
    - Ceccobelli, undated; 209453 (Album BC)
    - Chia, undated; 209454 (Album BD)
    - Commandeur, undated; 209455 (Album BD)
    - Condo, undated; 209456 (Album BD)
    - Connelly, undated; 209457 (Album BD)
    - Sold Connelly's, undated; 209458 (Album BD)
    - D, undated; 209459 (Album BE)
    - Duclos, undated; 209460 (Album BE)
    - F, undated; 209461 (Album BE)
    - Forg, undated; 209462 (Album BE)
    - Galan, undated; 209463 (Album BE)
    - Gallace, undated; 209464 (Album BE)
    - Kaufmann, undated; 209465 (Album BE)
    - Koberling, undated; 209466 (Album BE)
    - Jannis Kounellis, undated; 209467 (Album BE)
    - K, undated; 209468 (Album BE)
    - Kuitca, undated; 209469 (Album BE)
    - Hodgkins, undated; 209470 (Album BF)
    - Joseph Kosuth, undated; 209471 (Album BF)
    - G. Lang, undated; 209472 (Album BF)
    - Tomarchio Levi, undated; 209473 (Album BF)
    - Mattiacci, undated; 209474 (Album BF)
    - McCollum, undated; 209475 (Album BF)
    - [Mariani], undated; 209476 (Album BF)
    - Middendorf/Sold Middendorf, undated; 209477 (Album BF)
    - Mirri, undated; 209478 (Album BG)
    - Moses, undated; 209479 (Album BG)
    - Mueller, undated; 209480 (Album BG)
    - [Robert Morris], undated; 209481 (Album BG)
    - Newman, undated; 209482 (Album BH)
    - Nunzio, undated; 209483 (Album BH)
    - [Mueller], undated; 209484 (Album BH)
    - Ocampo, undated; 209485 (Album BH)
    - Ongaro, undated; 209486 (Album BH)
    - Paladino, undated; 209487 (Album BH)
    - Palmieri, undated; 209488 (Album BH)
    - R [Gert Rappenecker], undated; 209490 (Album BH)
    - Rayberry, undated; 209491 (Album BH)
    - Pizzi Cannella, undated; 209489 (Album BH)
    - Rammellzee, undated; 209492 (Album BH)
    - Ross, undated; 209493 (Album BI)
    - Rifka, undated; 209494 (Album BI)
    - Salvo, undated; 209495 (Album BI)
    - Cheri Samba, undated; 209496 (Album BI)
    - Schuyff, undated; 209497 (Album BI)
    - Sicilia, undated; 209498 (Album BI)
    - Stevens, undated; 209499 (Album BI)
    - Sonneman, undated; 209500 (Album BI)
    - Tirelli, undated; 209501 (Album BI)
    - T/Welsh, undated; 209502 (Album BI)
    - Salomé, undated; 209503 (Album BI)
    - Wizon, undated; 209504 (Album BI)
    - Kruger, undated; 209505 (Album BI)
    - Welling/[Elizondo], undated; 209506 (Album BI)
- Series IV: Jean-Michel Basquiat Artist File, 1981-2003; 200737
  Series comprises artist bios and other promotional material, price lists, invoices, correspondence, phone bills, bank account records, photographic material, and periodicals and clipping relating to Jean-Michel Basquiat, his work, and his relationship with the Annina Nosei Gallery.
  - Subseries A: Artist Files, 200743
    - Basquiat - Misc. Receipts, Tel. Bil, 1981-1983; 208188 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Basquiat Bio, Press Release, Prices, 1981-1989; 208189 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Press, 1981-1992; 208190 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - [Exhibition Cards and Announcements], 1982-2003; 208191 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - "Poems by JMB", undated; 208192 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence, 200744
    Correspondence mostly regarding Basquiat and Basquiat work. Three small pieces of correspondence from Basquiat.
    - Basquiat Correspondence 1982-1987 [1/2] [Material from Plastic Sleeve], 1982, 1983; 208193 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Contains two letters signed by Basquiat.
    - Basquiat Correspondence 1982-1987 [2/2], 208194 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Basquiat - Museums, 1981-1985; 208195 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - [Postcard Purportedly from Basquiat], undated; 208480 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Subseries C: Accounting, 200745
    - [Loose Material from "Basquiat Accounting" Letter Box], 1982; 208196 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Accounting Jean Michel Basquiat [From "Basquiat Accounting" Letter Box] [1/3], 1981-1983; 208197 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - [Contents of Plastic Sleeve from "Accounting Jean Michel Basquiat [1/3]"], 1981, 1982; 208198 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Accounting Jean Michel Basquiat [From "Basquiat Accounting" Letter Box] [2/3], 1982; 208199 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Accounting Jean Michel Basquiat [From "Basquiat Accounting" Letter Box] [3/3], 1982; 208200 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Subseries D: Invoices, 204166
    - [Basquiat - Invoices] [1/4], 1981, 1982; 208201 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - [Basquiat - Invoices] [2/4], 1982, 1983; 208202 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - [Basquiat - Invoices] [3/4], 1983-1985; 208203 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - [Basquiat - Invoices] [4/4], 1983-1987; 208204 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Subseries E: Slides Binder, 204167
    Original binder sleeves, when numbered, are included with their contents in the new binders.
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat [Material from Front Pocket of Slide Binder], undated; 209295 (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Slides, undated; 208994 (Album BJ)
  - Subseries F: Visuals Binders, 205263
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [1/3], undated; 208995 (Album BK)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [2/3], undated; 208996 (Album BL)